-DOCSTART- -X- O
Just -X- _ O
tried -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
new -X- _ O
coffee -X- _ O
at -X- _ O
Starbucks -X- _ B-ORG
, -X- _ O
absolutely -X- _ O
loved -X- _ O
it -X- _ O
! -X- _ O

Ca -X- _ O
n't -X- _ O
wait -X- _ O
for -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
# -X- _ O
AppleEvent -X- _ B-HASHTAG
next -X- _ O
week -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Visiting -X- _ O
Paris -X- _ B-LOC
in -X- _ O
December -X- _ B-DATE
, -X- _ O
any -X- _ O
tips -X- _ O
for -X- _ O
sightseeing -X- _ O
? -X- _ O

Check -X- _ O
out -X- _ O
my -X- _ O
blog -X- _ O
at -X- _ O
https -X- _ B-URL
: -X- _ I-URL
/ -X- _ I-URL
/ -X- _ I-URL
travelwithme.com -X- _ I-URL
for -X- _ O
travel -X- _ O
tips -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Congrats -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
@ -X- _ O
elonmusk -X- _ B-PERSON
for -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
SpaceX -X- _ B-ORG
launch -X- _ O
success -X- _ O
! -X- _ O

My -X- _ O
favorite -X- _ O
song -X- _ O
right -X- _ O
now -X- _ O
is -X- _ O
“Blinding -X- _ B-PRODUCT
Lights” -X- _ I-PRODUCT
by -X- _ O
The -X- _ B-PERSON
Weeknd -X- _ I-PERSON
. -X- _ O

Anyone -X- _ O
else -X- _ O
excited -X- _ O
for -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
FIFA -X- _ B-EVENT
World -X- _ I-EVENT
Cup -X- _ I-EVENT
2026 -X- _ I-EVENT
? -X- _ O

Bought -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
new -X- _ O
iPhone -X- _ B-PRODUCT
15 -X- _ I-PRODUCT
, -X- _ O
it’s -X- _ O
amazing -X- _ O
! -X- _ O

Throwback -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
my -X- _ O
graduation -X- _ B-DATE
day -X- _ I-DATE
at -X- _ O
Harvard -X- _ B-ORG
University -X- _ I-ORG
🎓 -X- _ O

Follow -X- _ O
me -X- _ O
for -X- _ O
daily -X- _ B-TIME
tech -X- _ O
updates -X- _ O
: -X- _ O
@ -X- _ O
techguru -X- _ B-PERSON

Watching -X- _ O
The -X- _ B-PRODUCT
Batman -X- _ I-PRODUCT
at -X- _ O
AMC -X- _ B-LOC
Theaters -X- _ I-LOC
tonight -X- _ B-TIME
🍿 -X- _ O

Shoutout -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
@ -X- _ O
nike -X- _ B-ORG
for -X- _ O
their -X- _ O
latest -X- _ B-PRODUCT
sneaker -X- _ I-PRODUCT
collection -X- _ I-PRODUCT
! -X- _ O

London -X- _ B-LOC
weather -X- _ O
is -X- _ O
crazy -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
November -X- _ B-DATE
🌧️ -X- _ O

Celebrating -X- _ O
Diwali -X- _ B-EVENT
with -X- _ O
family -X- _ O
this -X- _ B-DATE
year -X- _ I-DATE
🪔 -X- _ O

Just -X- _ O
posted -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
new -X- _ O
photo -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
Instagram -X- _ B-ORG
: -X- _ O
https -X- _ B-URL
: -X- _ I-URL
/ -X- _ I-URL
/ -X- _ I-URL
instagram.com -X- _ I-URL
/ -X- _ I-URL
p -X- _ I-URL
/ -X- _ I-URL
xyz -X- _ I-URL

Anyone -X- _ O
going -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
Coachella -X- _ B-LOC
2025 -X- _ B-DATE
? -X- _ O

My -X- _ O
favorite -X- _ O
YouTube -X- _ B-ORG
channel -X- _ O
is -X- _ O
MrBeast -X- _ B-PERSON
🎥 -X- _ O

Ordering -X- _ O
pizza -X- _ O
from -X- _ O
Domino’s -X- _ B-ORG
, -X- _ O
what -X- _ O
toppings -X- _ O
do -X- _ O
you -X- _ O
suggest -X- _ O
? -X- _ O

Happy -X- _ O
Birthday -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
my -X- _ O
best -X- _ O
friend -X- _ O
@ -X- _ O
sarah_jones -X- _ B-PERSON
! -X- _ O

Exploring -X- _ O
Tokyo -X- _ B-LOC
streets -X- _ O
at -X- _ O
night -X- _ B-TIME
, -X- _ O
neon -X- _ B-PRODUCT
lights -X- _ I-PRODUCT
everywhere -X- _ O
✨ -X- _ O

Love -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
new -X- _ O
features -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
Android -X- _ B-PRODUCT
14 -X- _ I-PRODUCT
OS -X- _ I-PRODUCT
. -X- _ O

Can’t -X- _ O
believe -X- _ O
it’s -X- _ O
been -X- _ O
10 -X- _ B-DATE
years -X- _ I-DATE
since -X- _ O
my -X- _ O
first -X- _ O
car -X- _ O
, -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
Toyota -X- _ B-PRODUCT
Corolla -X- _ I-PRODUCT
🚗 -X- _ O

Shoutout -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
@ -X- _ O
NASA -X- _ B-ORG
for -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
Mars -X- _ B-PRODUCT
Rover -X- _ I-PRODUCT
updates -X- _ O
! -X- _ O

Streaming -X- _ O
Stranger -X- _ B-PRODUCT
Things -X- _ I-PRODUCT
on -X- _ O
Netflix -X- _ B-ORG
tonight -X- _ B-TIME
. -X- _ O

Visit -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
official -X- _ O
website -X- _ O
: -X- _ O
https -X- _ B-URL
: -X- _ I-URL
/ -X- _ I-URL
/ -X- _ I-URL
www.nike.com -X- _ I-URL
/ -X- _ I-URL
sneakers -X- _ I-URL

Just -X- _ O
got -X- _ O
tickets -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
Taylor -X- _ B-PERSON
Swift’s -X- _ I-PERSON
concert -X- _ B-EVENT
in -X- _ O
Los -X- _ B-LOC
Angeles -X- _ I-LOC
! -X- _ O

Watching -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
sunset -X- _ B-TIME
at -X- _ O
Santorini -X- _ B-LOC
🌅 -X- _ O

Who -X- _ O
else -X- _ O
is -X- _ O
using -X- _ O
ChatGPT -X- _ B-PRODUCT
for -X- _ O
their -X- _ O
projects -X- _ O
? -X- _ O

Amazon -X- _ B-ORG
Prime -X- _ B-EVENT
Day -X- _ I-EVENT
deals -X- _ O
are -X- _ O
insane -X- _ O
! -X- _ O

Attending -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
TechCrunch -X- _ B-EVENT
Disrupt -X- _ I-EVENT
2024 -X- _ B-DATE
event -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Trying -X- _ O
out -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
new -X- _ O
Starbucks -X- _ B-ORG
Pumpkin -X- _ B-PRODUCT
Spice -X- _ I-PRODUCT
Latte -X- _ I-PRODUCT
🎃 -X- _ O

Follow -X- _ O
@ -X- _ O
BBCNews -X- _ B-ORG
for -X- _ O
latest -X- _ O
world -X- _ O
updates -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Hiking -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
Yosemite -X- _ B-LOC
National -X- _ I-LOC
Park -X- _ I-LOC
this -X- _ B-DATE
weekend -X- _ I-DATE
. -X- _ O

Just -X- _ O
shared -X- _ O
my -X- _ O
thoughts -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
LinkedIn -X- _ B-ORG
: -X- _ O
https -X- _ B-URL
: -X- _ I-URL
/ -X- _ I-URL
/ -X- _ I-URL
linkedin.com -X- _ I-URL
/ -X- _ I-URL
pulse -X- _ I-URL
/ -X- _ I-URL
abc -X- _ I-URL

Congrats -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
Oscar -X- _ B-EVENT
winners -X- _ O
this -X- _ B-DATE
year -X- _ I-DATE
! -X- _ O
🏆 -X- _ O

Love -X- _ O
listening -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
Billie -X- _ B-PERSON
Eilish’s -X- _ I-PERSON
new -X- _ B-PRODUCT
album -X- _ I-PRODUCT
on -X- _ O
Spotify -X- _ B-ORG
. -X- _ O

Visiting -X- _ O
New -X- _ B-LOC
York -X- _ I-LOC
City -X- _ I-LOC
in -X- _ O
April -X- _ B-DATE
. -X- _ O

Bought -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
new -X- _ O
MacBook -X- _ B-PRODUCT
Pro -X- _ I-PRODUCT
for -X- _ O
work -X- _ O
! -X- _ O

Can’t -X- _ O
wait -X- _ O
for -X- _ O
Comic-Con -X- _ B-EVENT
2025 -X- _ B-DATE
! -X- _ O

Watching -X- _ O
live -X- _ O
football -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
ESPN -X- _ B-ORG
tonight -X- _ B-TIME
⚽ -X- _ O

Shoutout -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
@ -X- _ O
adidas -X- _ B-ORG
for -X- _ O
their -X- _ O
latest -X- _ O
campaign -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Just -X- _ O
published -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
new -X- _ O
blog -X- _ O
post -X- _ O
about -X- _ O
AI -X- _ O
trends -X- _ O
: -X- _ O
https -X- _ B-URL
: -X- _ I-URL
/ -X- _ I-URL
/ -X- _ I-URL
aiblog.com -X- _ I-URL

Traveling -X- _ O
from -X- _ O
London -X- _ B-LOC
to -X- _ O
Rome -X- _ B-LOC
next -X- _ B-DATE
month -X- _ I-DATE
. -X- _ O

Happy -X- _ O
anniversary -X- _ O
@ -X- _ O
john_doe -X- _ B-PERSON
and -X- _ O
@ -X- _ O
jane_doe -X- _ B-PERSON
❤️ -X- _ O

The -X- _ B-LOC
Louvre -X- _ I-LOC
Museum -X- _ I-LOC
is -X- _ O
breathtaking -X- _ O
🖼️ -X- _ O

Following -X- _ O
@ -X- _ O
NASA_Hubble -X- _ B-ORG
for -X- _ O
space -X- _ O
photography -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Enjoying -X- _ O
pizza -X- _ O
at -X- _ O
Pizza -X- _ B-LOC
Hut -X- _ I-LOC
tonight -X- _ B-TIME
🍕 -X- _ O

Excited -X- _ O
for -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
launch -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
Tesla -X- _ B-PRODUCT
Model -X- _ I-PRODUCT
3 -X- _ I-PRODUCT
in -X- _ O
India -X- _ B-LOC
. -X- _ O

Reading -X- _ O
“Atomic -X- _ B-PRODUCT
Habits” -X- _ I-PRODUCT
by -X- _ O
James -X- _ B-PERSON
Clear -X- _ I-PERSON
. -X- _ O

Celebrating -X- _ O
New -X- _ B-EVENT
Year -X- _ I-EVENT
2025 -X- _ B-DATE
in -X- _ O
Sydney -X- _ B-LOC
🎆 -X- _ O

Can’t -X- _ O
wait -X- _ O
for -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
next -X- _ B-PRODUCT
Marvel -X- _ I-PRODUCT
movie -X- _ I-PRODUCT
! -X- _ O

Just -X- _ O
signed -X- _ O
up -X- _ O
for -X- _ O
AWS -X- _ B-EVENT
re -X- _ I-EVENT
: -X- _ I-EVENT
Invent -X- _ I-EVENT
2024 -X- _ B-DATE
. -X- _ O

Visiting -X- _ O
Disneyland -X- _ B-LOC
Paris -X- _ I-LOC
with -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
family -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Watching -X- _ O
live -X- _ O
updates -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
CNN -X- _ B-ORG
. -X- _ O

Attending -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
concert -X- _ B-EVENT
by -X- _ O
Ed -X- _ B-PERSON
Sheeran -X- _ I-PERSON
in -X- _ O
London -X- _ B-LOC
. -X- _ O

Just -X- _ O
tried -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
new -X- _ O
Oreo -X- _ B-PRODUCT
flavor -X- _ I-PRODUCT
, -X- _ O
so -X- _ O
good -X- _ O
! -X- _ O

Follow -X- _ O
me -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
TikTok -X- _ B-ORG
: -X- _ O
@ -X- _ O
dancewithme -X- _ B-PERSON

Going -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
gym -X- _ O
at -X- _ O
Gold’s -X- _ B-LOC
Gym -X- _ I-LOC
every -X- _ B-TIME
morning -X- _ I-TIME
. -X- _ O

Launching -X- _ O
my -X- _ O
startup -X- _ O
next -X- _ B-DATE
month -X- _ I-DATE
, -X- _ O
fingers -X- _ O
crossed -X- _ O
! -X- _ O

Happy -X- _ O
Thanksgiving -X- _ B-EVENT
from -X- _ O
my -X- _ O
family -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
yours -X- _ O
🦃 -X- _ O

Enjoying -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
sunny -X- _ B-TIME
day -X- _ I-TIME
at -X- _ O
Bondi -X- _ B-LOC
Beach -X- _ I-LOC
🏖️ -X- _ O

Bought -X- _ O
my -X- _ O
first -X- _ O
DSLR -X- _ B-PRODUCT
camera -X- _ I-PRODUCT
, -X- _ O
Canon -X- _ B-PRODUCT
EOS -X- _ I-PRODUCT
90D -X- _ I-PRODUCT
📷 -X- _ O

Following -X- _ O
@ -X- _ O
BBCSport -X- _ B-ORG
for -X- _ O
match -X- _ O
updates -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Excited -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
attend -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
CES -X- _ B-EVENT
2025 -X- _ B-DATE
tech -X- _ O
expo -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Reading -X- _ O
latest -X- _ O
news -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
https -X- _ B-URL
: -X- _ I-URL
/ -X- _ I-URL
/ -X- _ I-URL
www.nytimes.com -X- _ I-URL

Can’t -X- _ O
stop -X- _ O
listening -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
Drake’s -X- _ B-PERSON
new -X- _ B-PRODUCT
song -X- _ I-PRODUCT
. -X- _ O

Attending -X- _ O
Wimbledon -X- _ B-LOC
2025 -X- _ B-DATE
, -X- _ O
can’t -X- _ O
wait -X- _ O
🎾 -X- _ O

Just -X- _ O
ordered -X- _ O
from -X- _ O
KFC -X- _ B-ORG
, -X- _ O
craving -X- _ O
fried -X- _ B-PRODUCT
chicken -X- _ I-PRODUCT
🍗 -X- _ O

Shoutout -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
@ -X- _ O
Starbucks -X- _ B-ORG
for -X- _ O
amazing -X- _ O
customer -X- _ O
service -X- _ O
! -X- _ O

Visiting -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
Grand -X- _ B-LOC
Canyon -X- _ I-LOC
this -X- _ B-TIME
weekend -X- _ I-TIME
🌄 -X- _ O

Enjoying -X- _ O
sushi -X- _ B-PRODUCT
at -X- _ O
Sushi -X- _ B-LOC
Samba -X- _ I-LOC
tonight -X- _ B-TIME
🍣 -X- _ O

Just -X- _ O
finished -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
marathon -X- _ B-EVENT
in -X- _ O
Boston -X- _ B-LOC
🏃‍♂️ -X- _ O

Following -X- _ O
@ -X- _ O
WHO -X- _ B-ORG
for -X- _ O
health -X- _ O
updates -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Can’t -X- _ O
believe -X- _ O
it’s -X- _ O
raining -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
Miami -X- _ B-LOC
again -X- _ O
☔ -X- _ O

Sharing -X- _ O
my -X- _ O
artwork -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
DeviantArt -X- _ B-ORG
: -X- _ O
https -X- _ B-URL
: -X- _ I-URL
/ -X- _ I-URL
/ -X- _ I-URL
deviantart.com -X- _ I-URL
/ -X- _ I-URL
myart -X- _ I-URL

Excited -X- _ O
for -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
launch -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
Google -X- _ B-PRODUCT
Pixel -X- _ I-PRODUCT
10 -X- _ I-PRODUCT
. -X- _ O

Watching -X- _ O
live -X- _ O
cricket -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
Star -X- _ B-ORG
Sports -X- _ I-ORG
. -X- _ O

Happy -X- _ O
Holi -X- _ B-EVENT
everyone -X- _ O
! -X- _ O
🌈 -X- _ O

Just -X- _ O
attended -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
World -X- _ B-EVENT
Economic -X- _ I-EVENT
Forum -X- _ I-EVENT
in -X- _ O
Davos -X- _ B-LOC
. -X- _ O

Buying -X- _ B-LOC
tickets -X- _ I-LOC
for -X- _ I-LOC
Hamilton -X- _ I-LOC
in -X- _ I-LOC
New -X- _ I-LOC
York -X- _ I-LOC
. -X- _ I-LOC

Exploring -X- _ O
street -X- _ O
food -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
Bangkok -X- _ B-LOC
🍜 -X- _ O

Can’t -X- _ O
wait -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
see -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
new -X- _ O
Samsung -X- _ B-ORG
Galaxy -X- _ B-PRODUCT
foldable -X- _ I-PRODUCT
phone -X- _ I-PRODUCT
. -X- _ O

Following -X- _ O
@ -X- _ O
NASA -X- _ B-ORG
for -X- _ O
daily -X- _ O
space -X- _ O
updates -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Just -X- _ O
shared -X- _ O
a -X- _ O
new -X- _ O
reel -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
Instagram -X- _ B-ORG
: -X- _ O
https -X- _ B-URL
: -X- _ I-URL
/ -X- _ I-URL
/ -X- _ I-URL
instagram.com -X- _ I-URL
/ -X- _ I-URL
reel -X- _ I-URL
/ -X- _ I-URL
xyz -X- _ I-URL

Celebrating -X- _ O
Halloween -X- _ B-EVENT
with -X- _ O
friends -X- _ O
🎃 -X- _ O

Reading -X- _ O
“Sapiens” -X- _ B-PRODUCT
by -X- _ O
Yuval -X- _ B-PERSON
Noah -X- _ I-PERSON
Harari -X- _ I-PERSON
📖 -X- _ O

Watching -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
Formula -X- _ B-EVENT
1 -X- _ I-EVENT
Grand -X- _ I-EVENT
Prix -X- _ I-EVENT
live -X- _ O
🏎️ -X- _ O

Attending -X- _ O
SXSW -X- _ B-EVENT
2025 -X- _ I-EVENT
in -X- _ O
Austin -X- _ B-LOC
, -X- _ I-LOC
Texas -X- _ I-LOC
. -X- _ I-LOC

Shoutout -X- _ O
to -X- _ O
@ -X- _ O
Pepsi -X- _ B-ORG
for -X- _ O
their -X- _ O
new -X- _ O
ad -X- _ O
campaign -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Hiking -X- _ O
in -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
Rocky -X- _ B-LOC
Mountains -X- _ I-LOC
this -X- _ B-DATE
summer -X- _ I-DATE
. -X- _ O

Just -X- _ O
tried -X- _ O
vegan -X- _ B-PRODUCT
burgers -X- _ I-PRODUCT
from -X- _ O
Beyond -X- _ B-ORG
Meat -X- _ I-ORG
🍔 -X- _ O

Following -X- _ O
@ -X- _ O
TechCrunch -X- _ B-ORG
for -X- _ O
startup -X- _ O
news -X- _ O
. -X- _ O

Excited -X- _ O
for -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
next -X- _ O
season -X- _ O
of -X- _ O
The -X- _ B-PRODUCT
Witcher -X- _ I-PRODUCT
on -X- _ O
Netflix -X- _ B-ORG
. -X- _ O

Attending -X- _ O
the -X- _ O
Cannes -X- _ B-EVENT
Film -X- _ I-EVENT
Festival -X- _ I-EVENT
2025 -X- _ B-DATE
🎬 -X- _ O

Just -X- _ O
bought -X- _ O
concert -X- _ B-EVENT
tickets -X- _ O
for -X- _ O
BTS -X- _ B-PERSON
in -X- _ O
Seoul -X- _ B-LOC
! -X- _ O

Visiting -X- _ O
Kyoto -X- _ B-LOC
during -X- _ O
cherry -X- _ B-TIME
blossom -X- _ I-TIME
season -X- _ I-TIME
🌸 -X- _ O

Watching -X- _ O
live -X- _ O
updates -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
BBC -X- _ B-ORG
News -X- _ I-ORG
. -X- _ O

Can’t -X- _ O
wait -X- _ O
for -X- _ O
Halloween -X- _ B-EVENT
party -X- _ B-EVENT
at -X- _ O
my -X- _ O
friend’s -X- _ O
place -X- _ O
🎃 -X- _ O

Sharing -X- _ O
my -X- _ O
photography -X- _ O
on -X- _ O
Instagram -X- _ B-PERSON
: -X- _ O
@ -X- _ O
photo_world -X- _ B-PERSON

Enjoying -X- _ O
coffee -X- _ O
at -X- _ O
Costa -X- _ B-LOC
Coffee -X- _ I-LOC
this -X- _ B-TIME
morning -X- _ I-TIME
☕ -X- _ O

